Hello friends,
welcome.
In this video, I am going to give
you an overview of ICICI Prudential Life Insurance Company
and how the stock can show momentum. The stock is trading at a low
monthly timeframe.
I have plotted a 90-times chart for the
stock. First, if you see, the
stock is trading around its important level.
Friends, it was
taking multiple times support and continuing its upward
momentum. Previously,
if you see, you will get to
see the entire reaction zone here.
As soon as the stock broke out,
you will see that
as soon as the stock broke out, after that, there was a
fall due to Corona. Friends, we got to
see it from such a clean breaking level.
Now, if you see, it broke
out here again, tested it,
and it settled. Now, if you
see, what has it done here, it is
adding support. If I
convert it a little bit to the weekly timeframe, you can see it here.  You can see
how it is forming patterns
and exactly around its support we are
seeing a bounce in the stock.
I feel that from here onwards, the
stock can
continue its upward momentum around its
supports. If you are getting some stock, then
your first com is
converting it to the daily time frame and show me, so
I will first remove it and
I am getting to see an important pattern within it.
First of all, if you look at it, you will get to
see a head and shoulders pattern within it, friends, this is its
one shoulder, which is its left shoulder.
After that, if you look here, there is
its head and now if you
look at it, there is its right shoulder and I am
also seeing a successful breakout of it.
Talking about the neck line, it
is an important neck line, friends, this
is a complete neck line and if I talk about the lower support, from
where we are taking support, we are going to see the
neck line of our upper side.  If it can break then
this sub board area right now if you
guys look at it, then you have got to see a support
brush here, this
point of this is such a big bearing, so
I feel that from here
in the coming time, you can see a bad roof side.
Talking about stop loss,
near by, I will convert it a little into a longer time
frame, friends, if we
talk about plus, then my star plus is going to be near
420, I am going to place its stop
loss,
talk about the target around 420, if I will take multiple
targets inside it, then I can take this train line target,
talking about the first target,
friends, then my first target of near thinking 24 can be
inside it and the second
target is where this stock can go and it
can also show a reversal from there, so this
entire zone is going to be inside it,
again if you guys look at it, that is why I will focus on shortening
my stock lock around the entry point,
first
target 24 which you have restored
according to reward, second target of 52 and talk about stop loss
So, what percentage is the stock of 420,
friends, I am looking inside the stock, there is a stock loss of 11% and an upper side of 15%, there is a
stock board, if you guys will see it
in monthly time, if I convert it into a little longer time frame,
and similar
stocks which cool down, then
in the coming time I feel that
you
can see these stocks out performing, I show you this type of live analysis
daily, you guys can
go and learn daily videos on my channel, you
can understand why, in what
way the patterns have to be drafted,
plotting them, after that subscribe to the channel for daily
morning,
friends you will get it